top-site-list.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Top Site List Planet

Top Site List Planet (hereafter referred to as TSLP) is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our web site. You can access and browse our site without disclosing any of your personal data. We do not collect personal information about individuals, such as names and mailing or e-mail addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual and he or she has agreed to the terms under which we will use it.

### Disclosure of Information

TSLP will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We may use IP addresses to compile and provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and administer the site. This statistical information may also be related to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We collect only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect personal information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

TSLP does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customise web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Advertising networks used by TSLP may use additional cookies to collect anonymous information. For details about opting out of collection of anonymous information, please visit the following page: NAI Cookie Opt-out.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TSLP. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following page: [Google Cookie Opt-out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin).

### External Web Sites

Please note that TSLP contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and read the privacy statements of each web site that might collect personally identifying information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by TSLP.

## Add Your Site

Top site lists are a simple, but powerful system for exposing your site to millions. If accepted into our exclusive network this is a great opportunity to grow your site. 

__Add A Site

## Top Site List

Pick a unique URL: top-site-list.com/your-name. Add a custom logo and background. Your choice of over 275 styles for your toplist, or provide your own custom HTML layout.

__Create A List

## Hosting Stats

4,641 Top Site Lists  
250,964 Members  
1,054,206 Listed Websites  
313,893,360 Total Votes  
573,586,155 Total Hits  

__See The Top 100 Lists
